<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ram&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ram&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Bhaskar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:36:25 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/first_post/</guid>
      <description>Hello This is First Post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Digital Marketing: Integrating AI, GPTs, and Blockchain Technologies for and secure record of ad impressions and clicks.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-06-07-ai-gpt-blockchain-in-digital-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-06-07-ai-gpt-blockchain-in-digital-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The digital marketing landscape is constantly evolving, with new technologies and strategies emerging to help businesses stay ahead of the curve. In recent years, the integration of artificial intelligence (AI), generative pre-trained transformers (GPTs), and blockchain technologies has revolutionized the way marketers approach their campaigns. This comprehensive guide will delve into the technical aspects of these advanced digital marketing techniques, providing clear explanations and insights into how they can be effectively implemented.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing Your Own Language Model with DeepFloyd AI</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-05-18-create-your-own-ai-language-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-05-18-create-your-own-ai-language-model/</guid>
      <description>Designing Your Own Language Model with DeepFloyd AI Artificial Intelligence (AI) is indisputably transforming the landscape of virtually every industry, with Natural Language Processing (NLP) playing a significant role in this revolution. Language models, a primary component of NLP, are capable of understanding, generating, and interacting in human language. Today, we will embark on a journey to build our own language model using DeepFloyd AI, a state-of-the-art machine learning platform. 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Bard: A Large Language Model Chatbot</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-05-16-google-bard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-05-16-google-bard/</guid>
      <description>What is Google Bard? Google Bard is a large language model (LLM) chatbot developed by Google AI. It is trained on a massive dataset of text and code, and can generate text, translate languages, write different kinds of creative content, and answer your questions in an informative way. Bard is still under development, but it has learned to perform many kinds of tasks, including&#xA;I will try my best to follow your instructions and complete your requests thoughtfully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT vs. Humans: Delving Deeper into Technical and Brain Intelligence Aspects</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-05-07-ai-and-human-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-05-07-ai-and-human-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: The rise of sophisticated language models like OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT has prompted deeper discussions on the comparison of artificial and human intelligence. In this blog post, we delve into the technical aspects of ChatGPT and the workings of the human brain to gain a more nuanced understanding of their conversational abilities, strengths, and weaknesses.&#xA;- I. Technical aspects of ChatGPT Architecture: ChatGPT is based on the GPT-4 architecture, which utilizes a Transformer model with self-attention mechanisms to process and generate text.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepFloyd-IF: A Pixel-Based Triple-Cascaded Diffusion Model for Photorealistic Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-05-04-deepfloyid-if/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-05-04-deepfloyid-if/</guid>
      <description>IF-I-XL-v1.0 DeepFloyd-IF is a pixel-based text-to-image triple-cascaded diffusion model, that can generate pictures with new state-of-the-art for photorealism and language understanding. The result is a highly efficient model that outperforms current state-of-the-art models, achieving a zero-shot FID-30K score of 6.66 on the COCO dataset.&#xA;Inspired by Photorealistic Text-to-Image Diffusion Models with Deep Language Understanding&#xA;Model Details Developed by: DeepFloyd, StabilityAI Model type: pixel-based text-to-image cascaded diffusion model Cascade Stage: I Num Parameters: 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of AI: Introducing GPT-3.5 With Live Browsing</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-04-26-chat-gpt-with-browsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-04-26-chat-gpt-with-browsing/</guid>
      <description>The Next Frontier in Language Models - Accessing Real-time Information&#xA;Introduction In recent years, artificial intelligence (AI) and natural language processing (NLP) have made significant advancements with the help of powerful models like GPT-3. Now, OpenAI is taking a leap forward with the latest innovation: GPT-3.5 With Browsing, a model that not only understands natural language but can also access live information from the internet.&#xA;1. What is GPT-3.5 With Browsing?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implantable Brain Machines: The Future of Human-Computer Interaction</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-04-24-ibms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-04-24-ibms/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As technology continues to advance at an unprecedented rate, one area that has garnered significant interest is implantable brain machines. These devices have the potential to revolutionize the way we interact with computers, offering new possibilities in communication, education, and even healthcare. In this blog post, we will delve into the world of implantable brain machines, exploring their potential uses, benefits, and the ethical concerns surrounding their implementation.&#xA;What are Implantable Brain Machines?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually Computing Travel Times for Long-Distance Flights and Space Travel: Uncovering the Precise Power-Law Relationship between Travel Time and Distance</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-04-17-gpt3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-04-17-gpt3/</guid>
      <description>One day, a curious person (me) decided to explore an interesting question: how does the time it takes to travel from point A to point B scale with distance, in the real world? They knew that travel time would grow slower than linearly, but they wanted to know exactly how it scaled.&#xA;In an attempt to see how travel time scales with distance in the real world, taking into account the different modes of transport available for various distances, I decided to explore this question by randomly selecting points from the GeoLife dataset where people are actually present, primarily in Seattle and Beijing, but with occasional visits to other cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools for reconnaissance and footprinting</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-04-15-awesome-recon-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-04-15-awesome-recon-tools/</guid>
      <description>Recon Tools A compiled list of tools for reconnaissance and footprinting.&#xA;Contents Domain and Network Recon - Tools for grabbing network related information.&#xA;Personal Information and Email Footprinting - Tools for finding personal information such as social networks and emails as well as footprinting tools for mail.&#xA;Hacking with Google - Use Google commands to your advantage&#xA;Domain and Network Recon Robust tools for gathering domain and network information.&#xA;Programs and Web Applications ARIN Whois/RDAP - A public resource that allows a user to retrieve information about IP number resources, organizations, and Points of Contact registered with ARIN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of ZK-EVMs: How Ethereum&#39;s Multi-Client Philosophy Enables Continued Decentralization</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-04-10-how-ethereum-makes-decentralization-possible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-04-10-how-ethereum-makes-decentralization-possible/</guid>
      <description>My thoughts on EVMs Multi Client repository One important aspect of Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s security and decentralization is its multi-client philosophy. Instead of relying on a single reference client, Ethereum has a specification written in Python and multiple independent implementations of the spec called clients. Each node runs a consensus client to validate blocks and an execution client to check state transitions. Currently, no single client makes up more than two-thirds of either category.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced SEO with AI: How Machine Learning and Natural Language Processing Are Changing the Game</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-03-07-advanced-seo-with-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-03-07-advanced-seo-with-ai/</guid>
      <description>Search engine optimization (SEO) is the process of optimizing your website to rank higher in search engine results pages (SERPs). While the basic principles of SEO remain the same, the advent of artificial intelligence (AI) is changing the game. AI-powered SEO tools are now available that use machine learning and natural language processing (NLP) to help businesses improve their search engine rankings and increase traffic to their websites.&#xA;In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the benefits of using AI in SEO and provide examples of AI-powered SEO tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layer 1 for Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-03-03-layer-1-for-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-03-03-layer-1-for-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Layer 1 for Artificial Intelligence Exploring the Importance of AI-Generated Images in the Metaverse The metaverse, a virtual world where users interact with one another and digital objects in a shared environment, is rapidly becoming a reality. As technology continues to advance, the ability to create realistic and immersive virtual experiences is becoming increasingly important. One of the key components of this is the use of AI-generated images as inputs. These images play a crucial role in creating detailed, realistic environments, characters, and objects that enhance the user experience in the metaverse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Filecoin EVM (FEVM) is the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) virtualized as a runtime on top of the Filecoin Virtual Machine (FVM). Before understanding the FEVM you must be familiar with the regular EVM.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-01-20-fvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-01-20-fvm/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s it for The FVM enables developers to build many new use cases on top of and with the Filecoin network.&#xA;Data access control One advantage centralized storage solutions have over web3 services is that they can limit individual data access.&#xA;The FVM enables Filecoin network participants to do the same. Threshold encryption networks, like Medusa, can individually or programmatically govern who can access a data collection without any contracts or validators having access to the data themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAOs and the Future of Decentralization - Insights from Bhaskar Developer, ETHGlobal Fellow, and Vitalik Buterin, the founder of Ethereum</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2023-01-16-daos-are-not-corporations-where-decentralization-in-autonomous-organizations-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2023-01-16-daos-are-not-corporations-where-decentralization-in-autonomous-organizations-matters/</guid>
      <description>DAOs and the Future of Decentralization - Insights from Bhaskar - Developer, ETHGlobal Fellow, and Vitalik Buterin, the founder of Ethereum. Decentralized Autonomous Organizations (DAOs) are digital entities that operate on blockchain technology, and they have been gaining a lot of attention in recent years. Unlike traditional corporations, DAOs are decentralized, meaning that they operate on a consensus-based system where all members have an equal say in decision-making. This is where the term &amp;ldquo;autonomous&amp;rdquo; comes in, as DAOs are able to operate independently without the need for intermediaries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI and ChatGPT</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-12-21-chat-gpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-12-21-chat-gpt/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to OpenAI: OpenAI is a research organization that focuses on developing and promoting friendly artificial intelligence. It was founded in 2015 by a group of entrepreneurs, researchers, and philanthropists who wanted to ensure that AI could be aligned with human values and would be used for the benefit of all humanity.&#xA;Overview of ChatGPT: ChatGPT is a variant of the GPT (Generative Pre-training Transformer) language model developed by OpenAI. It is designed to generate human-like text in a conversational style, making it well-suited for tasks such as chatbots, dialog systems, and question answering systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strassen`s Algorithm</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-12-12-strassens-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-12-12-strassens-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>Multiplying Matrices #Standard Algorithm:&#xA;Matrix multiplication is one of the most fundamental and ubiquitous operations in all of mathematics. To multiply a pair of n-by-n matrices, each with n2 elements, you multiply and add these elements together in particular combinations to generate the product, a third n-by-n matrix. The standard recipe for multiplying two n-by-n matrices requires n3 multiplication operations, so a 2-by-2 matrix, for example, requires eight multiplications.&#xA;For larger matrices, with thousands of rows and columns, this process quickly becomes cumbersome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Princess Diana – The Twisted Truth and Ritual Sacrifice of the New World Order</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-11-28-princess-diana-investigation-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-11-28-princess-diana-investigation-report/</guid>
      <description>Princess Diana – The Twisted Truth and Ritual Sacrifice of the New World Order&#xA;25 years ago, Princess Diana’s car crashed inside the Pont de l’Alma Tunnel in Paris, France. Her lover, Dodi Fayed died upon impact along with the driver, and even though Diana survived, it took about 40 minutes to get her from the car. To the ambulance. The official story was that they were trying to free her from the car, but several witnesses say that Diana was conscious and unobstructed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Wi-Fi Scanner with Python and Scapy</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-11-09-creating-your-own-wifi-scanner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-11-09-creating-your-own-wifi-scanner/</guid>
      <description>Wi-Fi Hacking: Creating a Wi-Fi Scanner with Python and Scapy Although there are numerous tools to hack Wi-Fi (802.11), to create your own tools you will need to understand the Wi-Fi protocol. In a previous tutorial, I explained the various types of frames in Wi-Fi. Now we will use that information to crate our own Wi-Fi scanner very similar to the aircrack-ng suite&amp;rsquo;s airmon-ng or Kismet.&#xA;To begin, we will need to understand a bit about scapy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperledger Cactus Project moved to Cacti</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-11-05-tsc-approves-cactus-merging-into-cacti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-11-05-tsc-approves-cactus-merging-into-cacti/</guid>
      <description>TSC Approves Hyperledger Cactus as New Project By Michael Klein, Blockchain and Multiparty Systems Architecture Lead at Accenture, and Hart Montgomery, Fujitsu Laboratories. Building DLT integration protocol We are thrilled to announce that the open source Blockchain Integration Framework that Accenture and Fujitsu jointly contributed to Hyperledger Labs has been welcomed as the latest Hyperledger project. With this, the project receives a formal name, Hyperledger Cactus, and also benefits from the resources and promise of longevity that come with inclusion in the Hyperledger Greenhouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft sued for open-source piracy through GitHub Copilot</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-11-06-microsoft-sued-for-violating-open-source-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-11-06-microsoft-sued-for-violating-open-source-rules/</guid>
      <description>Programmer and lawyer Matthew Butterick has sued Microsoft, GitHub, and OpenAI, alleging that GitHub&amp;rsquo;s Copilot violates the terms of open-source licenses and infringes the rights of programmers.&#xA;GitHub Copilot, released in June 2022, is an AI-based programming aid that uses OpenAI Codex to generate real-time source code and function recommendations in Visual Studio.&#xA;The tool was trained with machine learning using billions of lines of code from public repositories and can transform natural language into code snippets across dozens of programming languages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google wants to become a key infrastructure provider for Web3</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-10-30-google-launched-blockchain-nodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-10-30-google-launched-blockchain-nodes/</guid>
      <description>Google Launches Cloud Node Engine For Ethereum Developers Google is launching a cloud-based node engine service for Ethereum developers and projects, the tech company announced Thursday.&#xA;Officially called Blockchain Node Engine, Google’s offering is a “fully managed service,” meaning customers won’t have to hire their own teams to maintain or monitor their nodes. Instead, Google says it “actively monitors the nodes and restarts them if anything goes wrong.”&#xA;The Blockchain Node Engine also includes various security features like Google’s Cloud Armor, which is designed to prevent denial-of-service (DDos) attacks that spam and slow down networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNOME 43 Endless Part In Its Creation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-10-14-gnome-43-endless-part-in-its-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-10-14-gnome-43-endless-part-in-its-creation/</guid>
      <description>GNOME 43 is out, and as always there is lots of good stuff in there. (Me circa 2014 would be delighted to see the continuous improvements in GNOME’s built-in RDP support.) During this cycle, the OS team at Endless OS Foundation spent a big chunk of our time on other initiatives, such as bringing Endless Key to more platforms and supporting the Endless Laptop programme. Even so, we made some notable contributions to this GNOME release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s new password less authentication technology</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-10-12-google-rolling-new-passwordless-authentication/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-10-12-google-rolling-new-passwordless-authentication/</guid>
      <description>Google Rolling Out Passkey Passwordless Login Support to Android and Chrome Google on Wednesday officially rolled out support for passkeys, the next-generation authentication standard, to both Android and Chrome.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Passkeys are a significantly safer replacement for passwords and other phishable authentication factors,&amp;rdquo; the tech giant said. &amp;ldquo;They cannot be reused, don&amp;rsquo;t leak in server breaches, and protect users from phishing attacks.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;To that end, creating a passkey requires confirmation from the end-user about the account that will be used to log in to the online service, followed by using their biometric information or the device passcode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Global Recession in 2023 Rises Amid Simultaneous Rate Hikes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-10-15-risk-of-global-recession-in-2023-rises-amid-simultaneous-rate-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-10-15-risk-of-global-recession-in-2023-rises-amid-simultaneous-rate-hikes/</guid>
      <description>Risk of Global Recession in 2023 Rises Amid Simultaneous Rate Hikes As central banks across the world simultaneously hike interest rates in response to inflation, the world may be edging toward a global recession in 2023 and a string of financial crises in emerging market and developing economies that would do them lasting harm, according to a comprehensive new study by the World Bank.&#xA;Central banks around the world have been raising interest rates this year with a degree of synchronicity not seen over the past five decades—a trend that is likely to continue well into next year, according to the report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trendlines With Breaks Script</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-10-08-trend-lines-with-breaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-10-08-trend-lines-with-breaks/</guid>
      <description>Trendlines With Breaks [Bhaskarvilles] by bhaskarvilles on TradingView.com&#xA;Chart As Image https://www.tradingview.com/i/d3HaLDmE/&#xA;Link to the Chart https://www.tradingview.com/script/d3HaLDmE-Trendlines-With-Breaks-Bhaskarvilles/</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New WhatsApp 0-Day Bug Let Hackers Execute a Code &amp; Take Full App Control Remotely</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-09-27-new-whatsapp-0-day-bug-can-access-whatsapp-remotely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-09-27-new-whatsapp-0-day-bug-can-access-whatsapp-remotely/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp silently fixed two critical zero-day vulnerabilities that affect both Android &amp;amp; iOS versions allowing attackers to execute an arbitrary code remotely.&#xA;Facebook-owned messenger WhatsApp is one of the Top-ranked Messenger apps with more than Billion users around the world in both Android and iPhone.&#xA;Both vulnerabilities are marked under “critical” severity with a CVE Score of 10/10 and found by the WhatsApp internal security Team.&#xA;Simplifying these following vulnerabilities, Whatsapp could cause your device to be hacked by receiving a Video File or When on a Video call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperledger Fabric Deployment — How We Aced it from Testing to Production</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-09-26-fabric-from-development-to-production/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-09-26-fabric-from-development-to-production/</guid>
      <description>You’ve set up your Dev environment, developed your chaincode, designed some decent looking UIs, and passed all your tests to get everything up &amp;amp; running locally. Now what? Is that everything you ever wanted? Of course not! You shouldn’t be satisfied at all. You need to do more. Your next target ought to be to scale the network and stimulate a production-level environment. Added to that, you should also focus on adding multiple orderers, organizations with their own peers and CAs, and try testing it on multiple machines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum 2.0 Merging</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-09-21-ethereum-2-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-09-21-ethereum-2-0/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum is moving to proof-of-stake! The transition, known as The Merge, must first be activated on the Beacon Chain with the Bellatrix upgrade. After this, the proof-of-work chain will migrate to proof-of-stake upon hitting a specific Total Difficulty value. The Bellatrix upgrade is scheduled for epoch 144896 on the Beacon Chain &amp;ndash; 11:34:47am UTC on Sept 6, 2022. The Terminal Total Difficulty value triggering The Merge is 58750000000000000000000, expected between Sept 10-20, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Engineering Attacks - Creating a Fake SMS Message</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-09-09-social-engineering-attacks-fake-sms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-09-09-social-engineering-attacks-fake-sms/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back, my aspiring cyber warriors!&#xA;Social engineering is a key feature of some of the biggest hacks in history! Many novice hackers are so focused upon mastering the technical aspects of hacking that they ignore at their own peril the power of social engineering. When nation-state actors such as Russia&amp;rsquo;s Sandworm hacking team (one of the most technically advanced hacker organizations) use social engineering to hack Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s electrical grid and the US 2016 Presidential election, that should be a sign that social engineering is important and critical to your hacking toolbox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Shifts to Paperless, Secure Procurement Contracts with Hyperledger Fabric</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/2022-09-07-hitachi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/2022-09-07-hitachi/</guid>
      <description>Read the full case study here.&#xA;Paper pushing. It’s synonymous with tedious, slow processes. Yet often, the pushed paper is vital to a company’s business. And contracts are especially important paper.&#xA;But digitizing a contract process isn’t as simple as it sounds. As the contract moves between parties, there’s a risk of tampering. Or mismanaging version control.&#xA;Many companies continue to use paper for their contracting processes to maintain security and trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital transformation - 4 key building blocks</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/digital_transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><author>bhaskarvilles@duck.com (Bhaskar)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/digital_transformation/</guid>
      <description>Here are four foundational elements on which to build your digital transformation strategy – plus a few barriers to avoid Digital transformation isn’t just about building great websites and mobile applications. It isn’t simply about providing a better user experience. While these are certainly critical enablers for success, truly reimagining how a business operates to thrive in a digital world requires much more – and skipping or failing to prioritize the “more” is where many organizations fall short of meeting their digital transformation goals.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
