<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ram&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ram&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Proposal to Extend NumPy Broadcasting for Enhanced Array Operations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/03/proposal-to-extend-numpy-broadcasting-for-enhanced-array-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/03/proposal-to-extend-numpy-broadcasting-for-enhanced-array-operations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;proposal-to-extend-numpy-broadcasting-for-d-d--n-m--d-d--k-m-when-k-is-a-multiple-of-n&#34;&gt;Proposal to Extend NumPy Broadcasting for (D₁, D₂, &amp;hellip;, N, M) → (D₁, D₂, &amp;hellip;, K, M) When K is a Multiple of N&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;proposal-enhancing-numpys-broadcasting-mechanism&#34;&gt;Proposal: Enhancing NumPy&amp;rsquo;s Broadcasting Mechanism&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;current-broadcasting-rule-and-its-limitation&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current Broadcasting Rule and Its Limitation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As per NumPy&amp;rsquo;s current broadcasting rules, if two arrays have different shapes, the smaller array can be expanded &lt;strong&gt;only if one of its dimensions is 1&lt;/strong&gt;. This allows memory-efficient expansion of data without copying. However, if a dimension is greater than 1, NumPy &lt;strong&gt;does not&lt;/strong&gt; allow expansion to a larger size, even when the larger size is a multiple of the smaller size.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS and iPadOS 18.4: A Comprehensive Overview of the Latest Updates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/03/ios-and-ipados-18.4-a-comprehensive-overview-of-the-latest-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/03/ios-and-ipados-18.4-a-comprehensive-overview-of-the-latest-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;ios-and-ipados-184-unveiling-the-latest-apple-updates&#34;&gt;iOS and iPadOS 18.4: Unveiling the Latest Apple Updates&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Apple has released iOS and iPadOS 18.4, bringing a host of new features, security improvements, and performance optimizations to its mobile ecosystem. This update represents Apple&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing user experience while maintaining the highest standards of security and privacy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-features-and-improvements&#34;&gt;Key Features and Improvements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;enhanced-privacy-and-security&#34;&gt;Enhanced Privacy and Security&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The latest update introduces several privacy-focused enhancements:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved private data redaction in system logs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced sandbox restrictions for better app isolation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Strengthened memory handling and input validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Advanced protection against malicious image processing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;system-optimizations&#34;&gt;System Optimizations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;iOS and iPadOS 18.4 bring various system-level improvements:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Power of Kerdos Vision AI for Image Generation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/03/unlocking-the-power-of-kerdos-vision-ai-for-image-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/03/unlocking-the-power-of-kerdos-vision-ai-for-image-generation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;kerdos-vision-ai-transforming-text-into-visual-masterpieces&#34;&gt;Kerdos Vision AI: Transforming Text into Visual Masterpieces&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the rapidly evolving landscape of AI-powered image generation tools, Kerdos Vision AI (&lt;a href=&#34;https://vision.kerdos.net.in&#34;&gt;https://vision.kerdos.net.in&lt;/a&gt;) emerges as an innovative platform that enables users to create stunning visual content through artificial intelligence. This groundbreaking technology represents a significant advancement in the field of AI-driven creative tools, making professional-quality image generation accessible to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-kerdos-vision-ai&#34;&gt;What is Kerdos Vision AI?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kerdos Vision AI is a state-of-the-art web-based platform that harnesses the power of artificial intelligence to generate images from textual descriptions. The platform provides an intuitive interface where users can input their creative ideas in the form of text prompts, and the AI transforms these descriptions into visually compelling images with remarkable accuracy and artistic flair.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerdos AI Launches Revolutionary Chat Application with OpenAI Integration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/03/kerdos-ai-launches-revolutionary-chat-application-with-openai-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/03/kerdos-ai-launches-revolutionary-chat-application-with-openai-integration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;kerdos-ai-revolutionizes-digital-communication-with-new-chat-application&#34;&gt;Kerdos AI Revolutionizes Digital Communication with New Chat Application&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a groundbreaking development for the artificial intelligence industry, Kerdos AI (&lt;a href=&#34;https://kerdos.xyz&#34;&gt;https://kerdos.xyz&lt;/a&gt;) has officially launched its highly anticipated chat application, marking a significant milestone in the evolution of AI-powered communication platforms. The application, which currently leverages OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s powerful API, promises to deliver an unparalleled conversational experience while setting the stage for even more innovative developments in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-new-era-of-intelligent-communication&#34;&gt;A New Era of Intelligent Communication&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The newly launched Kerdos AI Chat Application represents a perfect blend of sophisticated technology and user-friendly design. By integrating OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s advanced language models, the platform offers users access to one of the most capable AI conversational systems available today. The application stands out for its ability to understand context, provide nuanced responses, and maintain engaging, meaningful dialogues across a wide range of topics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Your Inner Drive: A Guide to Motivation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/03/finding-your-inner-drive-a-guide-to-motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/03/finding-your-inner-drive-a-guide-to-motivation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-unbreakable-flame-rising-when-the-world-pushes-you-down&#34;&gt;The Unbreakable Flame: Rising When the World Pushes You Down&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;March 10, 2025&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s a moment in every life—maybe it’s happened to you already—where the weight of the world feels like it’s crushing your chest. The plans you meticulously built collapse like a house of cards in a storm. The people you trusted turn their backs. The dreams you chased slip through your fingers like sand. You’re left staring at the wreckage, wondering, &lt;em&gt;“Why me?”&lt;/em&gt; or worse, &lt;em&gt;“What’s the point?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet Archive hacked, data breach impacts 31 million users</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/02/internet-archive-hacked-data-breach-impacts-31-million-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/02/internet-archive-hacked-data-breach-impacts-31-million-users/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;internet-archive-hacked-data-breach-impacts-31-million-users&#34;&gt;Internet Archive hacked, data breach impacts 31 million users&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Internet Archive, a non-profit digital library, has suffered a data breach affecting 31 million users. The breach involved the theft of user authentication data, including email addresses, screen names, password change timestamps, and Bcrypt-hashed passwords.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://help.archive.org/files/2022/09/ia-logo-2line-150w.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened&#34;&gt;What happened?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Internet Archive, a non-profit digital library, has suffered a data breach affecting 31 million users. The breach involved the theft of user authentication data, including email addresses, screen names, password change timestamps, and Bcrypt-hashed passwords.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running Local Large Language Models (LLMs) for Image Generation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/02/running-local-large-language-models-llms-for-image-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/02/running-local-large-language-models-llms-for-image-generation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;running-local-large-language-models-llms-for-image-generation-a-comprehensive-guide&#34;&gt;Running Local Large Language Models (LLMs) for Image Generation: A Comprehensive Guide&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In recent years, large language models (LLMs) have made significant strides in various applications, including text generation, translation, and even image creation. With the advent of tools like DALL-E, Stable Diffusion, and others, generating high-quality images from textual descriptions has become more accessible than ever. However, many users are now looking to run these models locally for reasons such as privacy concerns, faster processing times, and avoiding reliance on cloud services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Side of AI: Navigating Ethical Challenges in Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/12/the-dark-side-of-ai-navigating-ethical-challenges-in-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/12/the-dark-side-of-ai-navigating-ethical-challenges-in-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As artificial intelligence continues to reshape our world at an unprecedented pace, we find ourselves at a critical juncture. While AI promises revolutionary advances in healthcare, science, and daily life, it also presents serious challenges that demand our immediate attention. This post examines the darker aspects of AI technology, exploring its potential risks and ethical implications that often remain understated in mainstream discussions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;privacy-concerns-in-ai&#34;&gt;Privacy Concerns in AI&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-collection-and-surveillance&#34;&gt;Data Collection and Surveillance&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The scale of data collection in modern AI systems is staggering and often concerning:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building the Future of OpenSearch: Community-Driven Innovation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/11/building-the-future-of-opensearch-community-driven-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/11/building-the-future-of-opensearch-community-driven-innovation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OpenSearch, the open-source search and analytics suite forked from Elasticsearch, has been making significant strides in building a vibrant community-driven ecosystem. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how OpenSearch is shaping the future of search technology through collaboration and innovation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-community-initiatives&#34;&gt;Key Community Initiatives&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenSearch has embraced several important initiatives to foster community growth:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transparent Development Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Public roadmap discussions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Open design proposals&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Community-driven feature prioritization&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Innovation Focus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced search capabilities&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Advanced analytics features&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved security frameworks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;recent-developments&#34;&gt;Recent Developments&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project has seen exciting progress in multiple areas:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BHASKAR: Transforming India&#39;s Startup Ecosystem</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/bhaskar-transforming-indias-startup-ecosystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/bhaskar-transforming-indias-startup-ecosystem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-new-era-of-innovation-for-indias-startup-community&#34;&gt;A New Era of Innovation for India&amp;rsquo;s Startup Community&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the rapidly evolving landscape of Indian entrepreneurship, a groundbreaking platform has emerged to revolutionize the way startups operate, collaborate, and grow. The Bharat Startup Knowledge Access Registry, affectionately known as &lt;strong&gt;BHASKAR&lt;/strong&gt;, is set to redefine India&amp;rsquo;s startup ecosystem. This innovative digital platform brings together entrepreneurs, investors, mentors, policymakers, and other key players in a unified space, fostering unprecedented levels of collaboration and knowledge sharing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technical Deep Dive: How Claude AI Can Control Computers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/technical-deep-dive-how-claude-ai-can-control-computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/technical-deep-dive-how-claude-ai-can-control-computers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;technical-deep-dive-how-claude-ai-can-control-computers&#34;&gt;Technical Deep Dive: How Claude AI Can Control Computers&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Claude and other advanced AI models can interact with computer systems through carefully designed interfaces and APIs. This article explores the technical architecture and implementation details that make this possible, focusing on the security implications and practical considerations of allowing AI systems to control computers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;architecture-overview&#34;&gt;Architecture Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;core-components&#34;&gt;Core Components&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-language-model-interface&#34;&gt;1. Language Model Interface&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The foundation of Claude&amp;rsquo;s computer control capabilities starts with its language model interface. This component:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snapdragon 8 Elite: Revolutionizing Mobile Performance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/snapdragon-8-elite-revolutionizing-mobile-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/snapdragon-8-elite-revolutionizing-mobile-performance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;snapdragon-8-elite-the-future-of-mobile-computing&#34;&gt;Snapdragon 8 Elite: The Future of Mobile Computing&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Qualcomm has once again pushed the boundaries of mobile technology with the introduction of the Snapdragon 8 Elite Mobile Platform. This groundbreaking chip is set to transform on-device experiences, offering unprecedented performance, AI capabilities, and power efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;powerhouse-performance-with-qualcomm-oryon-cpu&#34;&gt;Powerhouse Performance with Qualcomm Oryon CPU&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the heart of the Snapdragon 8 Elite lies the all-new Qualcomm Oryon CPU, built from the ground up to deliver exceptional performance:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From $20 to $52,000 in 30 Days: Exploring the 20 Pips a Day Challenge Strategy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/from-20-to-52000-in-30-days-exploring-the-20-pips-a-day-challenge-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/from-20-to-52000-in-30-days-exploring-the-20-pips-a-day-challenge-strategy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;from-20-to-52000-in-30-days-exploring-the-20-pips-a-day-challenge-strategy&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From $20 to $52,000 in 30 Days: Exploring the 20 Pips a Day Challenge Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered if it’s possible to turn $20 into over $50,000 in just 30 days of trading? It sounds like a dream, right? Well, it might be possible with a fast account growth strategy known as the &lt;strong&gt;20 Pips a Day Challenge&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.freepik.com/free-vector/forex-trading-chart-background-exchange-digital-money-fund_1017-44910.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Trading Challenge&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This strategy was shared with me by a Patreon supporter, and after testing it thoroughly, I can say it’s one of the most intriguing approaches I’ve come across in my 8 years of trading. With the help of 1,000 trading bots using this exact strategy, I analyzed the performance and viability of this challenge. Here’s a detailed breakdown of the strategy, how it works, and the results I uncovered.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Remarkable Journey of a Japanese Trader: From $15K to $150 Million</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/the-remarkable-journey-of-a-japanese-trader-from-15k-to-150-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/the-remarkable-journey-of-a-japanese-trader-from-15k-to-150-million/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-remarkable-journey-of-a-japanese-trader-from-15k-to-150-million&#34;&gt;The Remarkable Journey of a Japanese Trader: From $15K to $150 Million&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the world of high-stakes trading, few stories capture the imagination quite like that of a Japanese trader known as BNF. His journey from starting with $15,000 to amassing a fortune of over $150 million is nothing short of legendary. The most astonishing part of his story? Making $17 million in under 10 minutes due to a mispricing error.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel&#39;s Air Strike on Damascus: Rising Tensions Amidst Iranian Influence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/israels-air-strike-on-damascus-rising-tensions-amidst-iranian-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/10/israels-air-strike-on-damascus-rising-tensions-amidst-iranian-influence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Israel&amp;rsquo;s Air Strike on Damascus: Rising Tensions Amidst Iranian Influence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On October 2, 2024, an Israeli air strike on a residential building in the Mazzeh neighborhood of Damascus claimed the lives of three individuals. According to the Britain-based Syrian Observatory for Human Rights, the attack targeted a flat reportedly frequented by Hezbollah leaders and members of the Iranian Revolutionary Guards. This strike is part of Israel&amp;rsquo;s ongoing efforts to prevent Iran&amp;rsquo;s influence from expanding within Syria.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Python Keylogger: A Security Researcher’s development to Understanding Keystroke Logging</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/building-a-python-keylogger-a-security-researchers-development-to-understanding-keystroke-logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/building-a-python-keylogger-a-security-researchers-development-to-understanding-keystroke-logging/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;setting-up-usb-autorun-for-testing&#34;&gt;Setting up USB Autorun (for testing):&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows&lt;/strong&gt;: You would need an &lt;code&gt;autorun.inf&lt;/code&gt; file on the USB, but keep in mind this is typically disabled by default for security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Linux/macOS&lt;/strong&gt;: You can set up a udev rule on Linux that triggers a script when a USB drive is inserted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s an example of how you might trigger your Python script on Linux when a USB drive is inserted using &lt;strong&gt;udev rules&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Event-Driven Architecture (EDA): How Netflix and Uber Handle Billions of Events Daily</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/the-power-of-event-driven-architecture-eda-how-netflix-and-uber-handle-billions-of-events-daily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/the-power-of-event-driven-architecture-eda-how-netflix-and-uber-handle-billions-of-events-daily/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-rise-of-event-driven-architecture-eda-in-modern-software-design&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Rise of Event-Driven Architecture (EDA) in Modern Software Design&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving digital landscape, the &lt;strong&gt;Event-Driven Architecture (EDA) pattern&lt;/strong&gt; has emerged as a cornerstone in modern software design, especially with the rise of &lt;strong&gt;microservices&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;big data&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;real-time processing&lt;/strong&gt;. Companies need scalable and flexible ways to handle interactions between different components, and EDA offers a robust solution. In this post, we’ll break down the EDA pattern, explore why it’s gaining popularity, and examine how leading companies like &lt;strong&gt;Netflix&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Uber&lt;/strong&gt; leverage this architecture to handle billions of events daily.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Customer Acquisition: Strategies for Small-Scale to Medium-Scale Industries</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/mastering-customer-acquisition-strategies-for-small-scale-to-medium-scale-industries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/mastering-customer-acquisition-strategies-for-small-scale-to-medium-scale-industries/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;customer-acquisition-for-small-scale-to-medium-scale-industries&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customer Acquisition for Small-Scale to Medium-Scale Industries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Customer acquisition is the lifeblood of any business. For small and medium-sized industries, the journey from merely surviving to thriving hinges on their ability to consistently attract, convert, and retain customers. In a world brimming with competition, standing out isn&amp;rsquo;t just an option—it&amp;rsquo;s a necessity. This guide dives deep into the strategies, tools, and insights needed to navigate the journey of customer acquisition, especially tailored for businesses aiming to scale from small to medium levels.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JSMON: Revolutionizing JavaScript Security Monitoring</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/jsmon-revolutionizing-javascript-security-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/jsmon-revolutionizing-javascript-security-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;jsmon-revolutionizing-javascript-security-monitoring&#34;&gt;JSMON: Revolutionizing JavaScript Security Monitoring&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today’s digital landscape, ensuring the security of JavaScript code across applications has become more important than ever. With increasing complexity in front-end development and APIs, JavaScript files often serve as a vector for attacks, exposing sensitive data and security flaws. &lt;strong&gt;JSMON&lt;/strong&gt; (jsmon.sh) has emerged as a leading security monitoring platform that addresses these challenges by providing a robust toolkit for analyzing JavaScript files. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a bug bounty hunter, penetration tester, or part of a security-focused enterprise, JSMON offers a comprehensive solution to track and manage JS vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why India Can&#39;t Yet Replicate the Success of Black Myth: Wukong in the AAA PC Game Market</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/why-india-cant-yet-replicate-the-success-of-black-myth-wukong-in-the-aaa-pc-game-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/why-india-cant-yet-replicate-the-success-of-black-myth-wukong-in-the-aaa-pc-game-market/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;title-why-india-can&#34;&gt;Title: &lt;em&gt;Why India Can&amp;rsquo;t Yet Replicate the Success of Black Myth: Wukong in the AAA PC Game Market&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In August 2024, &lt;em&gt;Black Myth: Wukong&lt;/em&gt;, a Chinese-developed game, set a record with 2.2 million concurrent players on Steam, surpassing every other single-player game in history. The game&amp;rsquo;s success is a testament not only to its quality but also to the business acumen behind it. While the gaming world celebrates this achievement, one question lingers: Can India create something similar?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing My Candidacy for the OWASP Global Board of Directors 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/announcing-my-candidacy-for-the-owasp-global-board-of-directors-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/announcing-my-candidacy-for-the-owasp-global-board-of-directors-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;announcing-my-candidacy-for-the-owasp-global-board-of-directors&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Announcing My Candidacy for the OWASP Global Board of Directors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://owasp.org/www-board-candidates/2024/bhaskar_ram_allam&#34;&gt;OWASP GLOBAL BOARD OF DIRECTORS 2024 ELECTIONS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am excited to officially announce my candidacy for the OWASP Global Board of Directors! With over a decade of experience in artificial intelligence, blockchain, and full-stack web development, I am passionate about advancing software security and expanding OWASP&amp;rsquo;s impact in the ever-evolving landscape of emerging technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-journey-in-technology-and-security&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Journey in Technology and Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the founder and leader of &lt;strong&gt;Kerdos Infrasoft Pvt Ltd&lt;/strong&gt;, I’ve had the opportunity to focus on innovations in blockchain technology and artificial intelligence, while working closely with some of the leading organizations in tech, such as the &lt;strong&gt;Linux Foundation, Hyperledger, OWASP&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;OpenAI&lt;/strong&gt;. Through these collaborations, I’ve developed a deep understanding of the critical importance of security in these technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Core of OpenAI o1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/the-core-of-openai-o1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/the-core-of-openai-o1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introducing OpenAI o1: A New Frontier in AI Reasoning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the rapidly evolving world of artificial intelligence, OpenAI has taken yet another bold step forward with the introduction of its latest series: &lt;strong&gt;OpenAI o1&lt;/strong&gt;. Released on September 12, 2024, this new model series is designed to handle complex reasoning tasks with a level of precision and depth previously unseen. With its enhanced capabilities in solving hard problems in science, coding, and math, OpenAI o1 represents a major advancement in the way AI tackles real-world challenges.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Airpods 4: Apple&#39;s next-generation wireless earbuds with improved audio quality, adaptive noise cancellation, and personalized spatial audio.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/apple-airpods-4-apples-next-generation-wireless-earbuds-with-improved-audio-quality-adaptive-noise-cancellation-and-personalized-spatial-audio./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/apple-airpods-4-apples-next-generation-wireless-earbuds-with-improved-audio-quality-adaptive-noise-cancellation-and-personalized-spatial-audio./</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introducing AirPods 4: A Leap Forward in Personalized Audio and Noise Cancellation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Apple’s newest release, the &lt;strong&gt;AirPods 4&lt;/strong&gt;, continues the company’s tradition of pushing boundaries in wireless audio technology. With enhanced features like &lt;strong&gt;Active Noise Cancellation&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Personalized Spatial Audio&lt;/strong&gt;, and improved battery life, AirPods 4 delivers a versatile and immersive listening experience. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re taking calls, listening to music, or enjoying a podcast, these wireless earbuds redefine what premium audio feels like. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at what makes AirPods 4 a standout in the world of wireless audio.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 &amp; Series 10 Watch: The rugged, high-performance smartwatch designed for extreme conditions, featuring a larger display, advanced sensors, and enhanced durability.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/apple-watch-ultra-2-series-10-watch-the-rugged-high-performance-smartwatch-designed-for-extreme-conditions-featuring-a-larger-display-advanced-sensors-and-enhanced-durability./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/apple-watch-ultra-2-series-10-watch-the-rugged-high-performance-smartwatch-designed-for-extreme-conditions-featuring-a-larger-display-advanced-sensors-and-enhanced-durability./</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exploring the Apple Watch Ultra 2: A Next-Gen Smartwatch for the Adventurer in You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Apple continues to push the boundaries of wearable technology with the launch of the &lt;strong&gt;Apple Watch Ultra 2&lt;/strong&gt;. Designed for fitness enthusiasts, adventurers, and tech lovers alike, this timepiece combines robust functionality with sleek aesthetics. In this blog post, we’ll dive into the standout features, performance specs, and why the Apple Watch Ultra 2 is an excellent companion for those leading active lifestyles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 16 Series: Apple&#39;s latest flagship smartphones, offering groundbreaking advancements in camera technology and performance with new features across four models.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/iphone-16-series-apples-latest-flagship-smartphones-offering-groundbreaking-advancements-in-camera-technology-and-performance-with-new-features-across-four-models./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/iphone-16-series-apples-latest-flagship-smartphones-offering-groundbreaking-advancements-in-camera-technology-and-performance-with-new-features-across-four-models./</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introducing the iPhone 16: The Future of Mobile Technology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Apple has once again redefined the smartphone experience with the launch of the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus. These devices bring groundbreaking innovations in design, performance, and intelligence, setting a new benchmark for what smartphones can do. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an Apple enthusiast or someone switching from Android, the iPhone 16 lineup is designed to meet the needs of a tech-driven world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASUS Gaming Devices: Unleashing the Power of Superior Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/asus-gaming-devices-unleashing-the-power-of-superior-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/09/asus-gaming-devices-unleashing-the-power-of-superior-services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;asus-gaming-devices-a-deep-dive-into-superior-performance-and-unmatched-services&#34;&gt;ASUS Gaming Devices: A Deep Dive into Superior Performance and Unmatched Services&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-the-asus-gaming-lineup-a-legacy-of-excellence&#34;&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;The ASUS Gaming Lineup: A Legacy of Excellence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ASUS has been a pioneer in the gaming industry, consistently pushing the boundaries of what gaming hardware can achieve. Their ROG (Republic of Gamers) and TUF (The Ultimate Force) series are renowned for their durability, cutting-edge technology, and gamer-centric designs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;11-rog-series-the-pinnacle-of-gaming-innovation&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.1 ROG Series: The Pinnacle of Gaming Innovation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ROG series is ASUS&amp;rsquo;s flagship gaming line, designed for hardcore gamers who demand nothing but the best. These devices are powered by the latest Intel Core or AMD Ryzen processors, paired with NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s GeForce RTX or AMD Radeon GPUs. This combination ensures that gamers can enjoy AAA titles at ultra-high settings with ray tracing and AI-enhanced graphics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering JavaScript Files with JSFinder</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/discovering-javascript-files-with-jsfinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/discovering-javascript-files-with-jsfinder/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;discovering-javascript-files-with-jsfinder&#34;&gt;Discovering JavaScript Files with JSFinder&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-need-for-javascript-discovery&#34;&gt;The Need for JavaScript Discovery&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;JavaScript is the backbone of modern web applications, driving dynamic behavior, interactivity, and user engagement. However, the same flexibility that makes JavaScript powerful also makes it a prime target for security vulnerabilities, such as cross-site scripting (XSS), data leakage, and unauthorized access. Identifying and analyzing JavaScript files across various subdomains is crucial for security researchers and developers aiming to secure their applications. Manual inspection of each subdomain is time-consuming and prone to errors, which is where automation tools like JSFinder come into play.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU&#39;s Stance on Lifting Restrictions for Kiev&#39;s Strikes on Russian Territory: Risks, Benefits, and Future Implications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/eus-stance-on-lifting-restrictions-for-kievs-strikes-on-russian-territory-risks-benefits-and-future-implications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/eus-stance-on-lifting-restrictions-for-kievs-strikes-on-russian-territory-risks-benefits-and-future-implications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-debate-over-lifting-eu-restrictions-on-kievs-strikes-on-russian-territory-analyzing-the-implications&#34;&gt;The Debate Over Lifting EU Restrictions on Kiev’s Strikes on Russian Territory: Analyzing the Implications&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ongoing conflict between Russia and Ukraine has reached a critical juncture, drawing the attention of global powers, especially within the European Union. The recent statements by Josep Borrell, the head of EU diplomacy, advocating for the complete lifting of restrictions on Kiev’s strikes on Russian territory, have sparked intense debates across diplomatic circles. These discussions have been further inflamed by Russia&amp;rsquo;s reaction, with the Russian Foreign Ministry Spokeswoman, Maria Zakharova, accusing the West of supporting Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s aggressive actions, including the attack on Russia’s Kursk region.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Side of AI in Call Summarization: Privacy, Personalization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/the-dark-side-of-ai-in-call-summarization-privacy-personalization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/the-dark-side-of-ai-in-call-summarization-privacy-personalization/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-dark-side-of-call-summarizing-ais-in-mobiles&#34;&gt;The Dark Side of Call Summarizing AIs in Mobiles&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today’s digital age, artificial intelligence (AI) is becoming increasingly pervasive, seamlessly integrating into various aspects of our lives. One such integration is the use of AI in mobile devices to summarize calls, a feature that promises convenience but comes with significant privacy and ethical concerns. Companies like Samsung (with Bixby), Apple (with Intelligence), and Jio (with Phonecall AI) have introduced this technology, touting it as a way to enhance user experience. However, the implications of these advancements go far beyond mere convenience. In this post, we will explore the dark side of call summarizing AIs, focusing on how they process data in the cloud, store it, and use it for personalization, targeted ads, and training large language models (LLMs).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced RISC Machines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/advanced-risc-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/advanced-risc-machines/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;arm-based-processors&#34;&gt;ARM-Based Processors&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARM (Advanced RISC Machines)&lt;/strong&gt; architecture refers to a family of reduced instruction set computing (RISC) architectures for processors, renowned for their power efficiency. ARM processors are distinct from traditional x86 processors (from companies like Intel and AMD) due to their focus on lower power consumption, making them especially suitable for mobile devices, embedded systems, and increasingly, high-performance computing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://media.geeksforgeeks.org/wp-content/uploads/20200711133437/Screenshot37.png&#34; alt=&#34;ARM Architecture&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;key-features-of-arm-based-processors&#34;&gt;Key Features of ARM-Based Processors:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power Efficiency&lt;/strong&gt;: ARM&amp;rsquo;s RISC architecture simplifies instructions and requires fewer transistors compared to x86 designs. This results in lower power consumption and less heat, critical for battery-powered devices.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scalability&lt;/strong&gt;: ARM processors are designed to scale across different uses, from tiny microcontrollers to powerful server CPUs. Companies can customize ARM architectures to suit their specific products.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customizability&lt;/strong&gt;: Original Equipment Manufacturers (OEMs) can license ARM architecture and create custom chips tailored for specific applications. Companies such as Qualcomm, Apple, and Samsung develop their system-on-chips (SoCs) based on ARM designs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Growing Ecosystem&lt;/strong&gt;: ARM processors have an ever-expanding ecosystem, supporting various applications from smartphone computing to data center operations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Performance Per Watt&lt;/strong&gt;: The ARM architecture has evolved significantly, offering excellent performance for every watt of power consumed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://static1.xdaimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/wm/2023/10/snapdragon-x-elite-6.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;snapdragon X Elite ARM based x64 processor hands-on&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running LLaMA 3.1 Locally with Ollama: A Step-by-Step process</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/running-llama-3.1-locally-with-ollama-a-step-by-step-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/running-llama-3.1-locally-with-ollama-a-step-by-step-process/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;running-llama-31-locally-with-ollama-a-step-by-step-process&#34;&gt;Running LLaMA 3.1 Locally with Ollama: A Step-by-Step process&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the rapid advancement in AI and machine learning, large language models (LLMs) have become an integral part of various applications, from chatbots to content generation. Meta’s LLaMA 3.1 (Large Language Model Meta AI) is one of the most powerful models available, and running it locally allows developers and researchers to explore its capabilities without relying on cloud-based services. One of the easiest ways to set up and run LLaMA 3.1 locally is using Ollama, a platform designed to streamline the deployment of LLMs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuation Urged in Ukrainian-Controlled DPR Cities: A Dire Call for Safety</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/evacuation-urged-in-ukrainian-controlled-dpr-cities-a-dire-call-for-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/evacuation-urged-in-ukrainian-controlled-dpr-cities-a-dire-call-for-safety/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;evacuation-urged-in-ukrainian-controlled-dpr-cities-a-dire-call-for-safety&#34;&gt;Evacuation Urged in Ukrainian-Controlled DPR Cities: A Dire Call for Safety&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a stark reminder of the ongoing conflict in Eastern Ukraine, Ukrainian Deputy Prime Minister Iryna Vereshchuk has issued an urgent call for the evacuation of residents from several cities under Ukrainian control in the Donetsk People&amp;rsquo;s Republic (DPR). The cities of Krasnoarmeysk, Dimitrov, and Selidovo are now in the crosshairs as the front line creeps dangerously closer, threatening the safety of thousands of civilians.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intercepting Mobile Calls: A Deep Dive into Threats to National Security</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/intercepting-mobile-calls-a-deep-dive-into-threats-to-national-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/intercepting-mobile-calls-a-deep-dive-into-threats-to-national-security/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intercepting-mobile-calls-a-deep-dive-into-threats-to-national-security&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intercepting Mobile Calls: A Deep Dive into Threats to National Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today’s interconnected world, mobile communication has become the backbone of personal and professional interactions. As mobile networks evolve from 2G to 5G, the need for secure communication channels has never been more critical. However, with advancements in technology, the risk of mobile call interception has also increased, posing significant threats to national security. This blog post explores the technical aspects of mobile call interception, the methods used by malicious actors, and the profound implications these have on national security.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower Documents Expose SEBI Chairperson&#39;s Alleged Involvement in the Adani Money Siphoning Scandal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/whistleblower-documents-expose-sebi-chairpersons-alleged-involvement-in-the-adani-money-siphoning-scandal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/whistleblower-documents-expose-sebi-chairpersons-alleged-involvement-in-the-adani-money-siphoning-scandal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;whistleblower-documents-expose-sebi-chairpersons-alleged-involvement-in-the-adani-money-siphoning-scandal&#34;&gt;Whistleblower Documents Expose SEBI Chairperson&amp;rsquo;s Alleged Involvement in the Adani Money Siphoning Scandal&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a scandal that could shake the foundations of India&amp;rsquo;s financial regulatory system, whistleblower documents have surfaced, implicating Madhabi Buch, the current Chairperson of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI), and her husband, Dhaval Buch, in the Adani money siphoning scandal. The revelations have come nearly 18 months after Hindenburg Research&amp;rsquo;s explosive report on the Adani Group, which accused the Indian conglomerate of operating &amp;ldquo;the largest con in corporate history.&amp;rdquo; The new documents suggest that SEBI&amp;rsquo;s apparent reluctance to pursue meaningful action against the Adani Group may stem from conflicts of interest involving its highest-ranking official.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US &amp; Islamists: A History of Connivance in Syria</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/the-us-islamists-a-history-of-connivance-in-syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/the-us-islamists-a-history-of-connivance-in-syria/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-us--islamists-a-history-of-connivance-in-syria&#34;&gt;The US &amp;amp; Islamists: A History of Connivance in Syria&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Syrian civil war (2011-2020) was a multifaceted conflict that involved a wide array of factions, including the Syrian government, various rebel groups, ISIS, and numerous international players. Among the narratives that emerged from this war is the contentious viewpoint that the United States and European Union supported jihadist groups to pressure the secular government of Bashar Assad. This post delves into key moments and decisions that allegedly facilitated the rise of Islamist groups, including ISIS, during the conflict.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Microservices Architecture: Benefits, Challenges, and Best Practices</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/exploring-microservices-architecture-benefits-challenges-and-best-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/08/exploring-microservices-architecture-benefits-challenges-and-best-practices/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microservices architecture has emerged as a dominant approach for designing and building complex software systems. Unlike monolithic architectures, where all components are tightly coupled and interdependent, microservices architecture structures an application as a collection of loosely coupled services, each responsible for a specific business capability. This blog post explores the benefits, challenges, and best practices for implementing microservices architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/includes/images/microservices-logical.png&#34; alt=&#34;Microservices Architecture&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-microservices&#34;&gt;What Are Microservices?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microservices are a style of software architecture where a large application is composed of small, independent services that communicate over well-defined APIs. Each service is responsible for a specific piece of functionality and can be developed, deployed, and scaled independently.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Artificial Neural Networks (ANNs) and Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/understanding-artificial-neural-networks-anns-and-convolutional-neural-networks-cnns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/understanding-artificial-neural-networks-anns-and-convolutional-neural-networks-cnns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;understanding-artificial-neural-networks-anns-and-convolutional-neural-networks-cnns&#34;&gt;Understanding Artificial Neural Networks (ANNs) and Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs)&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Neural networks have revolutionized the field of artificial intelligence and machine learning. Their ability to model complex patterns and relationships has led to significant advancements in various domains, from computer vision to natural language processing. Among the myriad types of neural networks, Artificial Neural Networks (ANNs) and Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) are two of the most prominent and widely used architectures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resilience in Custom Linux Distributions: A Solution to Microsoft Windows Outages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/resilience-in-custom-linux-distributions-a-solution-to-microsoft-windows-outages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/resilience-in-custom-linux-distributions-a-solution-to-microsoft-windows-outages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Windows outages can be disruptive and costly, underscoring the need for more resilient alternatives. Custom Linux distributions offer robust solutions, tailored to specific needs, reducing the risk of widespread system failures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.moneycontrol.com/static-mcnews/2024/07/20240719092012_windows.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Blue Screen Of Death&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-impact-of-microsoft-windows-outages&#34;&gt;The Impact of Microsoft Windows Outages&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Windows is widely used across various sectors, from personal computing to enterprise environments. However, its popularity also makes it a prime target for cyberattacks and system failures. Recent outages have shown that even minor disruptions can lead to significant productivity losses, highlighting the need for more robust and adaptable operating systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contributions to Open Source Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/contributions-to-open-source-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/contributions-to-open-source-projects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;contributions-overview&#34;&gt;Contributions Overview&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;nationalsecurityagencyghidra-3802&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/NationalSecurityAgency/ghidra/pull/3802&#34;&gt;NationalSecurityAgency/ghidra #3802&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Update run configurations and documentation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; This pull request updates the run configurations and documentation for Ghidra. It includes changes to enhance usability and address issues with existing configurations. The update aims to streamline the setup process for developers working with Ghidra.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;details&#34;&gt;Details:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This PR includes updates to the run configurations for Ghidra, addressing issues with existing setups and enhancing usability for developers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;filecoin-projectlotus-8204&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/filecoin-project/lotus/pull/8204&#34;&gt;filecoin-project/lotus #8204&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; feat: add snapshot creation to lotus-miner&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; This pull request adds a new feature to the Lotus miner, enabling snapshot creation. This feature allows for capturing the state of the miner at a specific point in time, which can be useful for backups, state inspection, and recovery purposes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;details-1&#34;&gt;Details:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adds functionality for creating snapshots of the miner&amp;rsquo;s state, facilitating easier backups and state inspections.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Knowledge Protocols (ZK)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/zero-knowledge-protocols-zk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/zero-knowledge-protocols-zk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;understanding-zero-knowledge-protocols&#34;&gt;Understanding Zero-Knowledge Protocols&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Zero-knowledge protocols are fascinating cryptographic systems that allow one party (the prover) to prove to another party (the verifier) that a given statement is true, without conveying any information apart from the fact that the statement is indeed true. This can have profound implications for privacy and security in digital communications and transactions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-are-zero-knowledge-proofs&#34;&gt;What are Zero-Knowledge Proofs?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Zero-knowledge proofs (ZKPs) are a method by which one party can prove to another that they know a value x, without conveying any information apart from the fact that they know the value x. The essence of ZKPs lies in the ability to verify the truthfulness of an assertion without revealing anything else about the underlying data.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS and iPadOS 18.4: A Comprehensive Overview of the Latest Updates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/03/ios-and-ipados-18.4-a-comprehensive-overview-of-the-latest-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/03/ios-and-ipados-18.4-a-comprehensive-overview-of-the-latest-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;// &amp;hellip; existing code &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Digital Marketing: Integrating AI, GPTs, and Blockchain Technologies for and secure record of ad impressions and clicks.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/06/advanced-digital-marketing-integrating-ai-gpts-and-blockchain-technologies-for-and-secure-record-of-ad-impressions-and-clicks./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/06/advanced-digital-marketing-integrating-ai-gpts-and-blockchain-technologies-for-and-secure-record-of-ad-impressions-and-clicks./</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The digital marketing landscape is constantly evolving, with new technologies and strategies emerging to help businesses stay ahead of the curve. In recent years, the integration of artificial intelligence (AI), generative pre-trained transformers (GPTs), and blockchain technologies has revolutionized the way marketers approach their campaigns. This comprehensive guide will delve into the technical aspects of these advanced digital marketing techniques, providing clear explanations and insights into how they can be effectively implemented.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing Your Own Language Model with DeepFloyd AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/designing-your-own-language-model-with-deepfloyd-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/designing-your-own-language-model-with-deepfloyd-ai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;designing-your-own-language-model-with-deepfloyd-ai&#34;&gt;Designing Your Own Language Model with DeepFloyd AI&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) is indisputably transforming the landscape of virtually every industry, with Natural Language Processing (NLP) playing a significant role in this revolution. Language models, a primary component of NLP, are capable of understanding, generating, and interacting in human language. Today, we will embark on a journey to build our own language model using DeepFloyd AI, a state-of-the-art machine learning platform.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://assets.forefront.ai/generated_images/12f68338-48f7-42ce-bd63-3babc6be5968-1684506464.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;AI&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Bard: A Large Language Model Chatbot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/google-bard-a-large-language-model-chatbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/google-bard-a-large-language-model-chatbot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-google-bard&#34;&gt;What is Google Bard?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Google Bard is a large language model (LLM) chatbot developed by Google AI. It is trained on a massive dataset of text and code, and can generate text, translate languages, write different kinds of creative content, and answer your questions in an informative way. Bard is still under development, but it has learned to perform many kinds of tasks, including&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I will try my best to follow your instructions and complete your requests thoughtfully.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I will use my knowledge to answer your questions in a comprehensive and informative way, even if they are open ended, challenging, or strange.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I will generate different creative text formats of text content, like poems, code, scripts, musical pieces, email, letters, etc. I will try my best to fulfill all your requirements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-use-google-bard-in-the-real-world&#34;&gt;How to Use Google Bard in the Real World&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Google Bard can be used in a variety of ways in the real world. Here are a few examples:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT vs. Humans: Delving Deeper into Technical and Brain Intelligence Aspects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/chatgpt-vs.-humans-delving-deeper-into-technical-and-brain-intelligence-aspects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/chatgpt-vs.-humans-delving-deeper-into-technical-and-brain-intelligence-aspects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction:&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The rise of sophisticated language models like OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT has prompted deeper discussions on the comparison of artificial and human intelligence. In this blog post, we delve into the technical aspects of ChatGPT and the workings of the human brain to gain a more nuanced understanding of their conversational abilities, strengths, and weaknesses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;--i-technical-aspects-of-chatgpt&#34;&gt;- I. Technical aspects of ChatGPT&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Architecture&lt;/strong&gt;: ChatGPT is based on the GPT-4 architecture, which utilizes a Transformer model with self-attention mechanisms to process and generate text. This allows it to understand and generate complex linguistic patterns effectively.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Training&lt;/strong&gt;: ChatGPT is trained on large datasets through unsupervised learning and fine-tuned  with supervised learning. This allows it to learn grammar, facts, and reasoning abilities by analyzing vast amounts of text data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous learning&lt;/strong&gt;: ChatGPT does not possess the ability to learn from new information after its training is completed. Its knowledge is static and limited to the training data it was exposed to.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;--ii-human-brain-intelligence-aspects&#34;&gt;- II. Human brain intelligence aspects&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neural networks&lt;/strong&gt;: The human brain consists of approximately 86 billion neurons, interconnected in complex networks. These networks enable humans to process and generate information, learn from experiences, and adapt to new situations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learning and memory&lt;/strong&gt;: Humans have the ability to learn and adapt throughout their lifetime, thanks to the process of synaptic plasticity. This allows them to accumulate knowledge and experience, which can be recalled and utilized in conversations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emotional and social intelligence&lt;/strong&gt;: The human brain is also responsible for managing emotions and social interactions, giving humans the ability to empathize and navigate complex social dynamics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;--iii-comparative-strengths-and-weaknesses&#34;&gt;- III. Comparative strengths and weaknesses&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ChatGPT strengths&lt;/strong&gt;: Fast response times, vast knowledge base, consistent performance, and multilingual capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ChatGPT weaknesses&lt;/strong&gt;: Limited understanding of context, lack of empathy, potential for bias, and inability to learn from new information.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Human strengths&lt;/strong&gt;: Emotional intelligence, creative problem-solving, adaptability, and lifelong learning.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Human weaknesses&lt;/strong&gt;: Limited knowledge base, inconsistency due to fatigue or emotions, and slower response times.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;--iv-implications-and-potential-applications&#34;&gt;- IV. Implications and potential applications&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Synergistic collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;: Combining the unique strengths of ChatGPT and human intelligence can lead to more effective solutions in domains like customer support, education, and mental health care.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personalized AI&lt;/strong&gt;: Integrating ChatGPT with human-like emotional intelligence could pave the way for more personalized AI experiences that cater to users&amp;rsquo; emotional needs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ethical considerations&lt;/strong&gt;: As AI systems like ChatGPT become more pervasive, it is crucial to address ethical concerns related to privacy, data security, job displacement, and the potential for AI-generated misinformation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A deeper understanding of the technical aspects of ChatGPT and the workings of the human brain reveals that both AI and human intelligence possess unique strengths and weaknesses in conversational abilities. By recognizing these differences and fostering collaborative approaches, we can harness the power of both AI and human intelligence to enhance communication, problem-solving, and innovation across diverse domains.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepFloyd-IF: A Pixel-Based Triple-Cascaded Diffusion Model for Photorealistic Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/deepfloyd-if-a-pixel-based-triple-cascaded-diffusion-model-for-photorealistic-text-to-image-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/deepfloyd-if-a-pixel-based-triple-cascaded-diffusion-model-for-photorealistic-text-to-image-generation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;if-i-xl-v10&#34;&gt;IF-I-XL-v1.0&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DeepFloyd-IF is a pixel-based text-to-image triple-cascaded diffusion model, that can generate pictures with new state-of-the-art for photorealism and language understanding. The result is a highly efficient model that outperforms current state-of-the-art models, achieving a zero-shot FID-30K score of &lt;code&gt;6.66&lt;/code&gt; on the COCO dataset.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inspired by&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/2205.11487.pdf&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photorealistic Text-to-Image Diffusion Models with Deep Language Understanding&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- ![](https://huggingface.co/DeepFloyd/IF-I-XL-v1.0/resolve/main/pics/deepfloyd_if_scheme.jpg) --&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;model-details&#34;&gt;Model Details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developed by:&lt;/strong&gt; DeepFloyd, StabilityAI&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model type:&lt;/strong&gt; pixel-based text-to-image cascaded diffusion model&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cascade Stage:&lt;/strong&gt; I&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Num Parameters:&lt;/strong&gt; 4.3B&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language(s):&lt;/strong&gt; primarily English and, to a lesser extent, other Romance languages&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;License:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:blue&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/spaces/DeepFloyd/deepfloyd-if-license&#34;&gt;DeepFloyd IF License Agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model Description:&lt;/strong&gt; DeepFloyd-IF is modular composed of frozen text mode and three pixel cascaded diffusion modules, each designed to generate images of increasing resolution: 64x64, 256x256, and 1024x1024. All stages of the model utilize a frozen text encoder based on the T5 transformer to extract text embeddings, which are then fed into a UNet architecture enhanced with cross-attention and attention-pooling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources for more information:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/deep-floyd/IF&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://deepfloyd.ai&#34;&gt;deepfloyd.ai&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://linktr.ee/deepfloyd&#34;&gt;All Links&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cite as (Soon):&lt;/strong&gt; -&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;using-with-diffusers&#34;&gt;Using with &lt;code&gt;diffusers&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;IF is integrated with the 🤗 Hugging Face &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/huggingface/diffusers/&#34;&gt;🧨 diffusers library&lt;/a&gt;, which is optimized to run on GPUs with as little as 14 GB of VRAM.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of AI: Introducing GPT-3.5 With Live Browsing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/04/the-evolution-of-ai-introducing-gpt-3.5-with-live-browsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/04/the-evolution-of-ai-introducing-gpt-3.5-with-live-browsing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Next Frontier in Language Models - Accessing Real-time Information&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In recent years, artificial intelligence (AI) and natural language processing (NLP) have made significant advancements with the help of powerful models like GPT-3. Now, OpenAI is taking a leap forward with the latest innovation: GPT-3.5 With Browsing, a model that not only understands natural language but can also access live information from the internet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bhaskarvilles/loveit-hugo/master/images/GPTSCREENSHOT.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;GPT-3.5-with-Browsing-Screenshot&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-what-is-gpt-35-with-browsing&#34;&gt;1. &lt;em&gt;What is GPT-3.5 With Browsing?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GPT-3.5 With Browsing is a groundbreaking language model that combines the power of GPT-3.5&amp;rsquo;s natural language understanding with the ability to browse the internet for real-time information. This means that the model can access and incorporate up-to-date information to provide better, more accurate responses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implantable Brain Machines: The Future of Human-Computer Interaction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/04/implantable-brain-machines-the-future-of-human-computer-interaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/04/implantable-brain-machines-the-future-of-human-computer-interaction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As technology continues to advance at an unprecedented rate, one area that has garnered significant interest is implantable brain machines. These devices have the potential to revolutionize the way we interact with computers, offering new possibilities in communication, education, and even healthcare. In this blog post, we will delve into the world of implantable brain machines, exploring their potential uses, benefits, and the ethical concerns surrounding their implementation.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mindmatters.ai/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/05/human-brain-with-an-implanted-chip-stockpack-adobe-stock-scaled.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Neural Brain&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually Computing Travel Times for Long-Distance Flights and Space Travel: Uncovering the Precise Power-Law Relationship between Travel Time and Distance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/04/manually-computing-travel-times-for-long-distance-flights-and-space-travel-uncovering-the-precise-power-law-relationship-between-travel-time-and-distance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/04/manually-computing-travel-times-for-long-distance-flights-and-space-travel-uncovering-the-precise-power-law-relationship-between-travel-time-and-distance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One day, a curious person (me) decided to explore an interesting question: how does the time it takes to travel from point A to point B scale with distance, in the real world? They knew that travel time would grow slower than linearly, but they wanted to know exactly how it scaled.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In an attempt to see how travel time scales with distance in the real world, taking into account the different modes of transport available for various distances, I decided to explore this question by randomly selecting points from the GeoLife dataset where people are actually present, primarily in Seattle and Beijing, but with occasional visits to other cities. Using public transport to travel between these points, I asked ChatGPT to write a script to extract a randomly selected coordinate from each file. While it did make the mistake of assuming every item in the list was a number, I fixed it manually.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools for reconnaissance and footprinting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/04/tools-for-reconnaissance-and-footprinting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/04/tools-for-reconnaissance-and-footprinting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;recon-tools&#34;&gt;Recon Tools&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A compiled list of tools for reconnaissance and footprinting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;contents&#34;&gt;Contents&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Domain-and-Network-Recon&#34;&gt;Domain and Network Recon&lt;/a&gt; - Tools for grabbing network related information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Personal-Information-and-Email-Footprinting&#34;&gt;Personal Information and Email Footprinting&lt;/a&gt; - Tools for finding personal information such as social networks and emails as well as footprinting tools for mail.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Hacking-with-Google&#34;&gt;Hacking with Google&lt;/a&gt; - Use Google commands to your advantage&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;domain-and-network-recon&#34;&gt;Domain and Network Recon&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Robust tools for gathering domain and network information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;programs-and-web-applications&#34;&gt;Programs and Web Applications&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arin.net/about/welcom/region&#34;&gt;ARIN Whois/RDAP&lt;/a&gt; - A public resource that allows a user to retrieve information about IP number resources, organizations, and Points of Contact registered with ARIN.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of ZK-EVMs: How Ethereum&#39;s Multi-Client Philosophy Enables Continued Decentralization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/04/the-rise-of-zk-evms-how-ethereums-multi-client-philosophy-enables-continued-decentralization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/04/the-rise-of-zk-evms-how-ethereums-multi-client-philosophy-enables-continued-decentralization/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-thoughts-on-evms-multi-client-repository&#34;&gt;My thoughts on EVMs Multi Client repository&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One important aspect of Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s security and decentralization is its multi-client philosophy. Instead of relying on a single reference client, Ethereum has a specification written in Python and multiple independent implementations of the spec called clients. Each node runs a consensus client to validate blocks and an execution client to check state transitions. Currently, no single client makes up more than two-thirds of either category. This ensures that bugs in any one client will not cripple the network.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced SEO with AI: How Machine Learning and Natural Language Processing Are Changing the Game</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/03/advanced-seo-with-ai-how-machine-learning-and-natural-language-processing-are-changing-the-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/03/advanced-seo-with-ai-how-machine-learning-and-natural-language-processing-are-changing-the-game/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Search engine optimization (SEO) is the process of optimizing your website to rank higher in search engine results pages (SERPs). While the basic principles of SEO remain the same, the advent of artificial intelligence (AI) is changing the game. AI-powered SEO tools are now available that use machine learning and natural language processing (NLP) to help businesses improve their search engine rankings and increase traffic to their websites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.weetechsolution.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Artificial-Intelligence-in-SEO.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the benefits of using AI in SEO and provide examples of AI-powered SEO tools. We&amp;rsquo;ll also explain how AI can help with content optimization and link building, and offer tips for implementing an AI-powered SEO strategy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layer 1 for Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/03/layer-1-for-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/03/layer-1-for-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;layer-1-for-artificial-intelligence&#34;&gt;Layer 1 for Artificial Intelligence&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://openfabric.ai/media/2023/01/AI_NFts.png&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;exploring-the-importance-of-ai-generated-images-in-the-metaverse&#34;&gt;Exploring the Importance of AI-Generated Images in the Metaverse&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The metaverse, a virtual world where users interact with one another and digital objects in a shared environment, is rapidly becoming a reality. As technology continues to advance, the ability to create realistic and immersive virtual experiences is becoming increasingly important. One of the key components of this is the use of AI-generated images as inputs. These images play a crucial role in creating detailed, realistic environments, characters, and objects that enhance the user experience in the metaverse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Filecoin EVM (FEVM) is the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) virtualized as a runtime on top of the Filecoin Virtual Machine (FVM). Before understanding the FEVM you must be familiar with the regular EVM.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/01/the-filecoin-evm-fevm-is-the-ethereum-virtual-machine-evm-virtualized-as-a-runtime-on-top-of-the-filecoin-virtual-machine-fvm.-before-understanding-the-fevm-you-must-be-familiar-with-the-regular-evm./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/01/the-filecoin-evm-fevm-is-the-ethereum-virtual-machine-evm-virtualized-as-a-runtime-on-top-of-the-filecoin-virtual-machine-fvm.-before-understanding-the-fevm-you-must-be-familiar-with-the-regular-evm./</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-it-for&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s it for&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The FVM enables developers to build many new use cases on top of and with the Filecoin network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-access-control&#34;&gt;Data access control&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One advantage centralized storage solutions have over web3 services is that they can limit individual data access.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The FVM enables Filecoin network participants to do the same. Threshold encryption networks, like Medusa, can individually or programmatically govern who can access a data collection without any contracts or validators having access to the data themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAOs and the Future of Decentralization - Insights from Bhaskar Developer, ETHGlobal Fellow, and Vitalik Buterin, the founder of Ethereum</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/12/daos-and-the-future-of-decentralization-insights-from-bhaskar-developer-ethglobal-fellow-and-vitalik-buterin-the-founder-of-ethereum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/12/daos-and-the-future-of-decentralization-insights-from-bhaskar-developer-ethglobal-fellow-and-vitalik-buterin-the-founder-of-ethereum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;daos-and-the-future-of-decentralization---insights-from-bhaskar---developer-ethglobal-fellow-and-vitalik-buterin-the-founder-of-ethereum&#34;&gt;DAOs and the Future of Decentralization - Insights from Bhaskar - Developer, ETHGlobal Fellow, and Vitalik Buterin, the founder of Ethereum.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Decentralized Autonomous Organizations (DAOs) are digital entities that operate on blockchain technology, and they have been gaining a lot of attention in recent years. Unlike traditional corporations, DAOs are decentralized, meaning that they operate on a consensus-based system where all members have an equal say in decision-making. This is where the term &amp;ldquo;autonomous&amp;rdquo; comes in, as DAOs are able to operate independently without the need for intermediaries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI and ChatGPT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/12/openai-and-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/12/openai-and-chatgpt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction-to-openai&#34;&gt;Introduction to OpenAI:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenAI is a research organization that focuses on developing and promoting friendly artificial intelligence. It was founded in 2015 by a group of entrepreneurs, researchers, and philanthropists who wanted to ensure that AI could be aligned with human values and would be used for the benefit of all humanity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/4/4d/OpenAI_Logo.svg/1280px-OpenAI_Logo.svg.png&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview-of-chatgpt&#34;&gt;Overview of ChatGPT:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ChatGPT is a variant of the GPT (Generative Pre-training Transformer) language model developed by OpenAI. It is designed to generate human-like text in a conversational style, making it well-suited for tasks such as chatbots, dialog systems, and question answering systems. ChatGPT is trained on a large dataset of human conversations and can generate responses to a wide range of prompts, including open-ended questions and prompts that require the model to provide information or perform a specific task.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strassen`s Algorithm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/12/strassens-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/12/strassens-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;multiplying-matrices&#34;&gt;Multiplying Matrices&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;#Standard Algorithm:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Matrix multiplication is one of the most fundamental and ubiquitous operations in all of mathematics. To multiply a pair of n-by-n matrices, each with n2 elements, you multiply and add these elements together in particular combinations to generate the product, a third n-by-n matrix. The standard recipe for multiplying two n-by-n matrices requires n3 multiplication operations, so a 2-by-2 matrix, for example, requires eight multiplications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bhaskarvilles/chirpy-images/main/STANDARD_ALGORITHM_MOBILE-cr.MerrillSherman-1.svg&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Princess Diana – The Twisted Truth and Ritual Sacrifice of the New World Order</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/princess-diana-the-twisted-truth-and-ritual-sacrifice-of-the-new-world-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/princess-diana-the-twisted-truth-and-ritual-sacrifice-of-the-new-world-order/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Princess Diana – The Twisted Truth and Ritual Sacrifice of the New World Order&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;25 years ago, Princess Diana’s car crashed inside the Pont de l’Alma Tunnel in Paris, France. Her lover, Dodi Fayed died upon impact along with the driver, and even though Diana survived, it took about 40 minutes to get her from the car. To the ambulance. The official story was that they were trying to free her from the car, but several witnesses say that Diana was conscious and unobstructed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Wi-Fi Scanner with Python and Scapy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/creating-a-wi-fi-scanner-with-python-and-scapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/creating-a-wi-fi-scanner-with-python-and-scapy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;wi-fi-hacking-creating-a-wi-fi-scanner-with-python-and-scapy&#34;&gt;Wi-Fi Hacking: Creating a Wi-Fi Scanner with Python and Scapy&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Although there are numerous tools to hack Wi-Fi (802.11), to create your own tools you will need to understand the Wi-Fi protocol. In a previous tutorial, I explained the various types of frames in Wi-Fi. Now we will use that information to crate our own Wi-Fi scanner very similar to the aircrack-ng suite&amp;rsquo;s airmon-ng or Kismet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://rashahacks.com/content/images/2022/11/6a4a49_7a739a0a2f1d4d2aaadc442e2142fd44-mv2.webp&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To begin, we will need to understand a bit about scapy. Scapy was written in Python and can  forge or decode packets, send them on the wire, capture them, and match requests and replies. It can also handle tasks like scanning, tracerouting, probing, unit tests, attacks, and network discovery. Scapy provides an interface to libpcap, the same library that Wireshark uses for packet capture and visualization. Scapy enables us then to grab packets and analyze for them for particular fields. So, for instance, if we were looking for beacon frames from an AP, we could filter for those with type 0 and subtype 8&#xA;This frame includes a variety of information including;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperledger Cactus Project moved to Cacti</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/hyperledger-cactus-project-moved-to-cacti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/hyperledger-cactus-project-moved-to-cacti/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tsc-approves-hyperledger-cactus-as-new-project&#34;&gt;TSC Approves Hyperledger Cactus as New Project&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;By Michael Klein, Blockchain and Multiparty Systems Architecture Lead at Accenture, and Hart Montgomery, Fujitsu Laboratories.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.hyperledger.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/HL_Website_TwitterImages_Cactus.png&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;building-dlt-integration-protocol&#34;&gt;Building DLT integration protocol&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to announce that the open source Blockchain Integration Framework that Accenture and Fujitsu jointly contributed to Hyperledger Labs has been welcomed as the latest Hyperledger project. With this, the project receives a formal name, Hyperledger Cactus, and also benefits from the resources and promise of longevity that come with inclusion in the Hyperledger Greenhouse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft sued for open-source piracy through GitHub Copilot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/microsoft-sued-for-open-source-piracy-through-github-copilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/microsoft-sued-for-open-source-piracy-through-github-copilot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.bleepstatic.com/content/hl-images/2021/05/10/GitHub-headpic.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Programmer and lawyer Matthew Butterick has sued Microsoft, GitHub, and OpenAI, alleging that GitHub&amp;rsquo;s Copilot violates the terms of open-source licenses and infringes the rights of programmers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GitHub Copilot, released in June 2022, is an AI-based programming aid that uses OpenAI Codex to generate real-time source code and function recommendations in Visual Studio.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The tool was trained with machine learning using billions of lines of code from public repositories and can transform natural language into code snippets across dozens of programming languages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google wants to become a key infrastructure provider for Web3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/10/google-wants-to-become-a-key-infrastructure-provider-for-web3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/10/google-wants-to-become-a-key-infrastructure-provider-for-web3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;google-launches-cloud-node-engine-for-ethereum-developers&#34;&gt;Google Launches Cloud Node Engine For Ethereum Developers&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Google is launching a cloud-based node engine service for Ethereum developers and projects, the tech company announced Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Officially called Blockchain Node Engine, Google’s offering is a “fully managed service,” meaning customers won’t have to hire their own teams to maintain or monitor their nodes. Instead, Google says it “actively monitors the nodes and restarts them if anything goes wrong.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Blockchain Node Engine also includes various security features like Google’s Cloud Armor, which is designed to prevent denial-of-service (DDos) attacks that spam and slow down networks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNOME 43 Endless Part In Its Creation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/10/gnome-43-endless-part-in-its-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/10/gnome-43-endless-part-in-its-creation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GNOME 43 is out, and as always there is lots of good stuff in there. (Me circa 2014 would be delighted to see the continuous improvements in GNOME’s built-in RDP support.) During this cycle, the OS team at Endless OS Foundation spent a big chunk of our time on other initiatives, such as bringing Endless Key to more platforms and supporting the Endless Laptop programme. Even so, we made some notable contributions to this GNOME release. Here are a few of them!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s new password less authentication technology</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/10/googles-new-password-less-authentication-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/10/googles-new-password-less-authentication-technology/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;google-rolling-out-passkey-passwordless-login-support-to-android-and-chrome&#34;&gt;Google Rolling Out Passkey Passwordless Login Support to Android and Chrome&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://thehackernews.com/new-images/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEigP4kNVXusoxtj-wk5GeI6xhh35bNbr78UBQVPz7STpEiye2petx9nDDVo87pS3J2OxNVyc8TC1rLUdSAT1V2z_xiawBgUsUlmqXSDCAH038SrP2Mo-hDfQlwp8luJShPB9P3PIzsNfStKo7PgGUTCDsODElL0TFKu1ZJQAJ3AZHiwR0BrSCNWm0jx/s728-e1000/login.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Google on Wednesday officially rolled out support for passkeys, the next-generation authentication standard, to both Android and Chrome.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Passkeys are a significantly safer replacement for passwords and other phishable authentication factors,&amp;rdquo; the tech giant said. &amp;ldquo;They cannot be reused, don&amp;rsquo;t leak in server breaches, and protect users from phishing attacks.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To that end, creating a passkey requires confirmation from the end-user about the account that will be used to log in to the online service, followed by using their biometric information or the device passcode.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Global Recession in 2023 Rises Amid Simultaneous Rate Hikes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/10/risk-of-global-recession-in-2023-rises-amid-simultaneous-rate-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/10/risk-of-global-recession-in-2023-rises-amid-simultaneous-rate-hikes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;risk-of-global-recession-in-2023-rises-amid-simultaneous-rate-hikes&#34;&gt;Risk of Global Recession in 2023 Rises Amid Simultaneous Rate Hikes&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As central banks across the world simultaneously hike interest rates in response to inflation, the world may be edging toward a global recession in 2023 and a string of financial crises in emerging market and developing economies that would do them lasting harm, according to a comprehensive new study by the World Bank.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Central banks around the world have been raising interest rates this year with a degree of synchronicity not seen over the past five decades—a trend that is likely to continue well into next year, according to the report. Yet the currently expected trajectory of interest-rate increases and other policy actions may not be sufficient to bring global inflation back down to levels seen before the pandemic. Investors expect central banks to raise global monetary-policy rates to almost 4 percent through 2023—an increase of more than 2 percentage points over their 2021 average.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trendlines With Breaks Script</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/10/trendlines-with-breaks-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/10/trendlines-with-breaks-script/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- TradingView Chart BEGIN --&gt;&#xA;&lt;script type=&#34;text/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#xA;&lt;script type=&#34;text/javascript&#34;&gt;&#xA;var tradingview_embed_options = {};&#xA;tradingview_embed_options.width = &#39;640&#39;;&#xA;tradingview_embed_options.height = &#39;400&#39;;&#xA;tradingview_embed_options.chart = &#39;d3HaLDmE&#39;;&#xA;new TradingView.chart(tradingview_embed_options);&#xA;&lt;/script&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tradingview.com/script/d3HaLDmE-Trendlines-With-Breaks-Bhaskarvilles/&#34;&gt;Trendlines With Breaks [Bhaskarvilles]&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tradingview.com/u/bhaskarvilles/&#34;&gt;bhaskarvilles&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tradingview.com/&#34;&gt;TradingView.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- TradingView Chart END --&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;chart-as-image&#34;&gt;Chart As Image&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tradingview.com/i/d3HaLDmE/&#34;&gt;https://www.tradingview.com/i/d3HaLDmE/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;link-to-the-chart&#34;&gt;Link to the Chart&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tradingview.com/script/d3HaLDmE-Trendlines-With-Breaks-Bhaskarvilles/&#34;&gt;https://www.tradingview.com/script/d3HaLDmE-Trendlines-With-Breaks-Bhaskarvilles/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New WhatsApp 0-Day Bug Let Hackers Execute a Code &amp; Take Full App Control Remotely</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/new-whatsapp-0-day-bug-let-hackers-execute-a-code-take-full-app-control-remotely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/new-whatsapp-0-day-bug-let-hackers-execute-a-code-take-full-app-control-remotely/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WhatsApp silently fixed two critical zero-day vulnerabilities that affect both Android &amp;amp; iOS versions allowing attackers to execute an arbitrary code remotely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i0.wp.com/blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEhyqCX58BbzMt4b6AorcIFMeo51MA8QTbY-UKNN2-xETgunEOyZMXjIZx95yi9szSSQPXA6PuDhvpqutIJ2AHIsmtrokxs6tt7_XuZugAnDq132gz7MCW-tsYQTXXNUzVhd7pD4d01D821IcyCN321Kko15fmlssSZQBAq89z6lw4yRej_6EPwdqwBzNQ/s16000/WhatsApp%200-Day%20Bug.png&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Facebook-owned messenger WhatsApp is one of the Top-ranked Messenger apps with more than Billion users around the world in both Android and iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both vulnerabilities are marked under “critical” severity with a CVE Score of 10/10 and found by the WhatsApp internal security Team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Simplifying these following vulnerabilities, Whatsapp could cause your device to be hacked by receiving a Video File or When on a Video call.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperledger Fabric Deployment — How We Aced it from Testing to Production</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/hyperledger-fabric-deployment-how-we-aced-it-from-testing-to-production/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/hyperledger-fabric-deployment-how-we-aced-it-from-testing-to-production/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ve set up your Dev environment, developed your chaincode, designed some decent looking UIs, and passed all your tests to get everything up &amp;amp; running locally. Now what? Is that everything you ever wanted? Of course not! You shouldn’t be satisfied at all. You need to do more. Your next target ought to be to scale the network and stimulate a production-level environment. Added to that, you should also focus on adding multiple orderers, organizations with their own peers and CAs, and try testing it on multiple machines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum 2.0 Merging</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/ethereum-2.0-merging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/ethereum-2.0-merging/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ethereum is moving to proof-of-stake! The transition, known as The Merge, must first be activated on the Beacon Chain with the Bellatrix upgrade. After this, the proof-of-work chain will migrate to proof-of-stake upon hitting a specific Total Difficulty value.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Bellatrix upgrade is scheduled for epoch 144896 on the Beacon Chain &amp;ndash; 11:34:47am UTC on Sept 6, 2022.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Terminal Total Difficulty value triggering The Merge is 58750000000000000000000, expected between Sept 10-20, 2022.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Note: as announced earlier, the Kiln testnet is being sunset. Operators will shut down on September 6, 2022.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bhaskarvilles/chirpy-images/8b6e67b1083da49817878039a3d040194fbdbebd/commons/https___storage.googleap_ethereum.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;alt&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Engineering Attacks - Creating a Fake SMS Message</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/social-engineering-attacks-creating-a-fake-sms-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/social-engineering-attacks-creating-a-fake-sms-message/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome back, my aspiring cyber warriors!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Social engineering is a key feature of some of the biggest hacks in history! Many novice hackers are so focused upon mastering the technical aspects of hacking that they ignore at their own peril the power of social engineering. When nation-state actors such as Russia&amp;rsquo;s Sandworm hacking team (one of the most technically advanced hacker organizations)  use social engineering to hack Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s electrical grid and the US 2016 Presidential election, that should be a sign that social engineering is important and critical to your hacking toolbox.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Shifts to Paperless, Secure Procurement Contracts with Hyperledger Fabric</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/hitachi-shifts-to-paperless-secure-procurement-contracts-with-hyperledger-fabric/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/hitachi-shifts-to-paperless-secure-procurement-contracts-with-hyperledger-fabric/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the full case study &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hyperledger.org/learn/publications/hitachi-case-study&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Paper pushing. It’s synonymous with tedious, slow processes. Yet often, the pushed paper is vital to a company’s business. And contracts are especially important paper.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But digitizing a contract process isn’t as simple as it sounds. As the contract moves between parties, there’s a risk of tampering. Or mismanaging version control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many companies continue to use paper for their contracting processes to maintain security and trust. The procurement divisions of Hitachi, Ltd. were no different.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital transformation - 4 key building blocks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/digital-transformation-4-key-building-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/09/digital-transformation-4-key-building-blocks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;here-are-four-foundational-elements-on-which-to-build-your-digital-transformation-strategy--plus-a-few-barriers-to-avoid&#34;&gt;Here are four foundational elements on which to build your digital transformation strategy – plus a few barriers to avoid&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Digital transformation isn’t just about building great websites and mobile applications. It isn’t simply about providing a better user experience. While these are certainly critical enablers for success, truly reimagining how a business operates to thrive in a digital world requires much more – and skipping or failing to prioritize the “more” is where many organizations fall short of meeting their digital transformation goals.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
