<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Security on Ram's Website</title><link>https://secretcoder.org/categories/security/</link><description>Recent content in Security on Ram's Website</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://secretcoder.org/categories/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JSMON: Revolutionizing JavaScript Security Monitoring</title><link>https://secretcoder.org/2024/09/jsmon-revolutionizing-javascript-security-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://secretcoder.org/2024/09/jsmon-revolutionizing-javascript-security-monitoring/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="jsmon-revolutionizing-javascript-security-monitoring">JSMON: Revolutionizing JavaScript Security Monitoring&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In today’s digital landscape, ensuring the security of JavaScript code across applications has become more important than ever. With increasing complexity in front-end development and APIs, JavaScript files often serve as a vector for attacks, exposing sensitive data and security flaws. &lt;strong>JSMON&lt;/strong> (jsmon.sh) has emerged as a leading security monitoring platform that addresses these challenges by providing a robust toolkit for analyzing JavaScript files. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a bug bounty hunter, penetration tester, or part of a security-focused enterprise, JSMON offers a comprehensive solution to track and manage JS vulnerabilities.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Discovering JavaScript Files with JSFinder</title><link>https://secretcoder.org/2024/08/discovering-javascript-files-with-jsfinder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://secretcoder.org/2024/08/discovering-javascript-files-with-jsfinder/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="discovering-javascript-files-with-jsfinder">Discovering JavaScript Files with JSFinder&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="the-need-for-javascript-discovery">The Need for JavaScript Discovery&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>JavaScript is the backbone of modern web applications, driving dynamic behavior, interactivity, and user engagement. However, the same flexibility that makes JavaScript powerful also makes it a prime target for security vulnerabilities, such as cross-site scripting (XSS), data leakage, and unauthorized access. Identifying and analyzing JavaScript files across various subdomains is crucial for security researchers and developers aiming to secure their applications. Manual inspection of each subdomain is time-consuming and prone to errors, which is where automation tools like JSFinder come into play.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contributions to Open Source Projects</title><link>https://secretcoder.org/2024/07/contributions-to-open-source-projects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://secretcoder.org/2024/07/contributions-to-open-source-projects/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="contributions-overview">Contributions Overview&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="nationalsecurityagencyghidra-3802">&lt;a href="https://github.com/NationalSecurityAgency/ghidra/pull/3802">NationalSecurityAgency/ghidra #3802&lt;/a>&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Title:&lt;/strong> Update run configurations and documentation&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Summary:&lt;/strong> This pull request updates the run configurations and documentation for Ghidra. It includes changes to enhance usability and address issues with existing configurations. The update aims to streamline the setup process for developers working with Ghidra.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="details">Details:&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>This PR includes updates to the run configurations for Ghidra, addressing issues with existing setups and enhancing usability for developers.&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="filecoin-projectlotus-8204">&lt;a href="https://github.com/filecoin-project/lotus/pull/8204">filecoin-project/lotus #8204&lt;/a>&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Title:&lt;/strong> feat: add snapshot creation to lotus-miner&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Summary:&lt;/strong> This pull request adds a new feature to the Lotus miner, enabling snapshot creation. This feature allows for capturing the state of the miner at a specific point in time, which can be useful for backups, state inspection, and recovery purposes.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="details-1">Details:&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Adds functionality for creating snapshots of the miner&amp;rsquo;s state, facilitating easier backups and state inspections.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Google's new password less authentication technology</title><link>https://secretcoder.org/2022/10/googles-new-password-less-authentication-technology/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://secretcoder.org/2022/10/googles-new-password-less-authentication-technology/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="google-rolling-out-passkey-passwordless-login-support-to-android-and-chrome">Google Rolling Out Passkey Passwordless Login Support to Android and Chrome&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://thehackernews.com/new-images/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEigP4kNVXusoxtj-wk5GeI6xhh35bNbr78UBQVPz7STpEiye2petx9nDDVo87pS3J2OxNVyc8TC1rLUdSAT1V2z_xiawBgUsUlmqXSDCAH038SrP2Mo-hDfQlwp8luJShPB9P3PIzsNfStKo7PgGUTCDsODElL0TFKu1ZJQAJ3AZHiwR0BrSCNWm0jx/s728-e1000/login.jpg" alt="alt">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Google on Wednesday officially rolled out support for passkeys, the next-generation authentication standard, to both Android and Chrome.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Passkeys are a significantly safer replacement for passwords and other phishable authentication factors,&amp;rdquo; the tech giant said. &amp;ldquo;They cannot be reused, don&amp;rsquo;t leak in server breaches, and protect users from phishing attacks.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To that end, creating a passkey requires confirmation from the end-user about the account that will be used to log in to the online service, followed by using their biometric information or the device passcode.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>